Guide to the Frank Lyon Polk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Partial Index to Series I
  - Costa Rica
    - Anderson, Chandler P., 1917
    - Fernández Guardia, Ricardo, 1917
    - Moses, George H., 1919
    - Noble, Herbert, 1917
    - Tumulty, Joseph P., 1919
  - Cuba
    - Andujar, Anthony, 1917
    - Baruch, Bernard M., 1917
    - Brooks, Sydney, 1915, 1917
    - Ferrara, Orestes, 1917
    - Fuller, Paul, Jr., 1919
    - Gonzales, William E., 1916, 1919
    - Hayes, George B., 1917-1919
    - Howell, Thomas A., 1918
    - Lakin, Herbert C., 1917
    - Larkin, Adrian H., 1918
    - Lewis, [Myron Henry?], 1918
    - Littleton, Martin W., 1917
    - Scholle, Gustave, 1917
    - Tumulty, Joseph P., 1919
  - Czechoslovakia
    - Billy, Esouard de, 1917
    - Masaryk, Tomáš G., 1918
    - Palmer, Frederick, 1917
    - Pergler, Charles, 1918
  - Denmark
    - Bernheimer, Charles L., 1917
    - Burn, Constantin, 1915-1918
    - Gale, William H., 1917
    - Grew, Joseph C., 1920
    - Haight, Sandford and Smith, 1915-1916
    - Hapgood, Norman, 1919
    - Munson, Frank C., 1917
    - Skinner, Robert P., 1915-1916
  - Dominican Republic
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1919
  - Economic Questions
    - Filene, Edward A., 1919
  - Ecuador
    - Belt, John W., 1919
  - Egypt
    - Crabites, Pierre, 1918
    - Gary, Hampson, 1918-1919
  - El Salvador
    - Long, Boaz, 1917
  - Election of 1916
    - Lansing, Robert, 1916
    - Logan, Thomas F., 1916
    - McCormick, Vance C., 1916
    - Sherley, Swagar, 1916
  - Election of 1920
    - Saxe, John G., 1920
  - Far East
    - Anderson, Larz, 1917
    - Arnold, Julian, 1916
    - Denby, Charles, 1918
    - Harrison, Francis B., 1916, 1918
    - Ishii, Kikujiro, 1919
    - Long, Breckinridge, 1919
    - Oudin, Maurice A., 1917
    - Rea, George B., 1920
    - Reinsch, Paul S., 1918-1919
    - Robinson, Joe T., 1919
    - Straight, Willard, 1917
    - Wadsworth, James W., 1920
  - Finance
    - Hitchcock, Gilbert M., 1919
    - Warburg, Paul M., 1920
    - White, John B., 1919
  - France
    - Billy, Edouard de, 1918
    - Bliss, Robert W., 1917
    - Eustis, Edith L., 1918
    - Gillet, Charles J., 1918
    - Grew, Joseph C., 1919-1920
    - Grimprel, U., 1918
    - Henry, Jules, 1917
    - Jusserand, Jean, 1916-1920
    - Jusserand, Elise, 1916
    - Réquin, Édouard, 1918
    - Simon, Joseph, 1918
    - Tardieu, André, 1918-1919
    - Wallace, Hugh C., 1920
  - Germany
    - Allen, Henry T., 1919
    - Davis, Norman H., 1920
    - Johnston, J., 1919
    - Kohlsaat, Herman H., 1919
    - Lersner, Kurt von, 1919
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1920
    - Miller, David H., 1920
    - Noyes, Pierrepont B., 1919
    - Pershing, John J., 1919
    - Phillips, William, 1919
    - Shepardson, Whitney, 1919
    - Swanson, Claude A., 1919
    - Warburg, Paul M., 1919
  - Great Britain
    - Barclay, Colville, 1915-1919
    - Bennet, William S., 1917
    - Broderick, John J., 1917-1918
    - Crawford, Richard, 1916-1918
    - Davis, John W., 1919-1921
    - Gaunt, Guy C., 1917
    - Grey, Edward, 1920
    - Hazard, William A., 1917
    - Hohler, Thomas B., 1917
    - Hudson, Robert S., 1918
    - Laughlin, Irwin B., 1916-1918
    - Lindsay, Ronald C., 1919-1920
    - McAneny, Marjorie J., 1917
    - Malcolm, Ian, 1917
    - Nevill, Richard, 1918
    - Osborne, D. G., 1917
    - Page, Walter Hines, 1916-1918
    - Percy, Eustace, 1917
    - Reading, Rufus D. I., 1918
    - Spring-Rice, Cecil Arthur, 1915-1918
    - Warren, Charles, 1917
  - Greece
    - Aravantinos, Panos, 1917
    - Balfour, Arthur James, 1919
    - Bowman, Isaiah, 1920
    - Cassavetes, Nicholas J., 1920
    - Chabot, Frederic C., 1918-1919
    - Droppers, Garrett, 1920
    - Romanos, A., 1919
    - Venizelos, Eleutherios, 1919
  - Guatemala
    - McNab, Gavin, 1919
  - Haiti
    - Clark, Benjamin P., 1915
  - Honduras
    - Belt, John W., 1917
    - Bonilla, Policarpo, 1919
    - Jones, T. Gambola, 1920
    - Suazo, Luis, 1919
  - Hungary
    - Bandholtz, Harry Hill, 1919
    - DuBois, Arthur W., 1919
  - Inquiry, The
    - Mezes, Sidney E., 1917-1918
    - Miller, David H., 1917
  - Interallied Conference
    - Bullitt, William C., 1917
  - Interior Department
    - Lane, Franklin, 1917, 1919
  - Ireland
    - Fletcher, Duncan U., 1918-1919
    - Mullins, Thomas D., 1919
    - O'Ceallaigh, Séan Z., 1919
    - Rasquin, William, 1916, 1919
  - Italy
    - Anderson, T. Hart, Jr., 1917
    - Avezzana, Camillo, 1920
    - Bowman, Isaiah, 1919
    - Brambilla, Giuseppe, 1919
    - Cellere, Vincenzo di, 1916-1918
    - Clark, Charles U., 1919-1920
    - Fay, [I. W.?], 1918
    - Ferraris, Maggiorino, 1919
    - Gibson, Hugh, 1918
    - Gotthardi, Ruggero, 1919
    - Grew, Joseph C., 1919
    - Hartigan, Joseph, 1919
    - Jay, Pierre, 1919
    - Johnson, Douglas W., 1920
    - Johnson, Evan M., 1919
    - Page, Thomas N., 1918
    - Stewart, William A. W., 1918
    - Tittoni, Tommaso, 1919
    - White, Henry, 1919
  - Labor Department
    - Wilson, William B., 1919
  - Latin America
    - Barrett, John, 1920
    - Bowman, Isaiah, 1920
    - Calder, William M., 1919
    - Carlton, Newcomb, 1917
    - Pan American Union, 1918-1919
    - Rowe, Leo S., 1919-1920
    - Stabler, Jordan H., 1919
  - League of Nations
    - Brandegee, Frank B., 1919
    - Caffey, Francis G., 1920
    - Dix, William C., 1919
    - Dulles, John F., 1919
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1919-1920
    - Gilbert, Cass, 1919
    - Hitchcock, Gilvert M., 1919
    - Houston, David F., 1920
    - Long, Breckinridge, 1919
    - Root, Elihu, 1919
    - Sweetser, Arthur, 1920
    - Shepardson, Whitney, 1919
    - Woolsey, Lester H., 1919
  - Mandates
    - Clemenceau, Georges, 1919
  - Mexico
    - Aguilar, Candido, 1919
    - Blanquet, Aurelio, 1919
    - Bliss, Tasker H., 1916
    - Bonillas, Ygnacio, 1917
    - Bonsal, Stephen, 1916
    - Burleson, Albert S., 1916
    - Cobb, Zach Lamar, 1916-1918
    - Crist, Harris M., 1917
    - Douglas, Charles A., 1916, 1919
    - Fletcher, Henry P., 1917-1918
    - Flournoy, James C., 1918
    - Garrison, Lindley M., 1919
    - Gavit, John P., 1916
    - Gay, Edward J., 1919
    - Haff, Delbert J., 1918
    - Hapgood, Norman, 1916
    - Harding, William P., 1918
    - Harvey, George, 1916
    - Hobby, William P., 1919
    - Hohler, Thomas B., 1915-1917
    - Kellogg, Frederick R., 1919
    - Klaessig, Emil, 1917
    - Lane, Franklin K., 1916
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1916
    - Logan, Thomas F., 1919
    - McLemore, Jefferson A., 1917
    - Malone, Dudley F., 1919
    - Marshall, H. Snowden, 1916
    - Meloy, Andrew D., 1916
    - Murray, Robert H., 1917
    - Neale, S. C., 1916
    - Potter, Howard, 1916
    - Robertson, Randolph, 1917
    - Sibbet, H. A., 1916
    - Stallforth, F., 1916
    - Strauss, Albert, 1917
    - Walker, Harold, 1917
    - Watriss, Frederic N., 1916-1920
  - Military Intelligence
    - Churchill, Marlborough, 1919
  - Motion Pictures, Censorship of
    - Bell, George H., 1917
  - Navy Department
    - Auchincloss, Gordon, 1919
    - Benson, William S., 1916
    - Carnegie, Thomas M., 1918
    - Daniels, Josephus, 1919
    - Gleaves, Albert, 1919
    - Graves, Ransom F., 1920
    - McCully, N. A., 1919
    - Pratt, William V., [1918?]
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1915-1919
    - Welles, Roger, 1918
  - Near East
    - Bristol, Mark L., 1919-1920
    - Buckler, William H., 1919-1920
    - Harrison, Leland, [1918-1920]
    - Lewin-Epstein, Elijah W., 1918
    - Patchin, Philip H., 1918-1919
    - Sokolow, Nahum, 1919
    - Tumulty, Joseph P., 1920
  - Netherlands
    - Boissevain, G. Louis, 1917
    - Churchill, Thomas W., 1919
    - Goldman, Sachs and Co., 1915-1916
    - Hill, David J., 1915
    - Kohns, Lee, 1917
    - Rappard, W.L.F.C. van, 1916
    - Stone, William J., 1917
    - Van Dyke, Henry, 1916
  - New York City
    - Block, Rudolph, 1917
    - Brooklyn Times, 1915
    - Fish, Stuyvesant, 1915
    - Harvier, Ernest, 1916
    - Lord, Franklin B., 1916
    - Newton, Byron R., 1918
  - Norway
    - Whipple, Sherman L., 1918
  - Panama
    - Baker, Newton D., 1917
    - Porras, Belisario, 1919
  - Peace Conference
    - Abraham, Edgar, 1919
    - Bayne, Hugh A., [1919-1920]
    - Cespedes, Carlos Manuel de, 1919
    - Clerk, George, 1919
    - Cléry, Cochin de, 1919
    - Curtis, Frazier, 1919
    - Dulles, Allen W., 1919
    - Faramond, ____, 1919
    - Grew, Joseph C., 1919
    - Guillaumeau, G., 1919
    - Kerr, Philip H., 1919
    - Mirasson, [G.?] de, 1919
    - Newton, Byron R., 1919
    - Shepardson, Whitney, 1919
    - Stevens, Guy, 1919
  - Peace Efforts
    - Balch, Emily G., 1916
    - Bernheimer, Charles L., 1915
    - Brougham, Herbert B., 1916-1917
    - Lewis, James H., 1918
    - Moores, Merrill, 1916
    - Riker, Carroll L., 1915
  - Poland
    - Carew, John F., 1919
    - Gibson, Hugh, 1919-1920
    - Hoover, Herbert C., 1921
    - Paderewski, Ignacy, 1919
    - Woolsey, Lester H., 1920
  - Post Office Department
    - Brady, Peter L., 1915
    - Burleson, Albert S., 1916
    - Burlingham, Charles C., 1916
    - Edwards, William, 1915
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1915-1916
    - Freaney, James G., 1915-1916
  - Press
    - Brougham, Herbert B., 1917
    - Hall, Henry M., 1917
    - Hills, Lawrence, [1919-1920]
    - Lauzanne, Stéphane, 1919
    - New York Times, 1919
    - Parker, Louis A., 1919
  - Puerto Rico
    - Gregory, Thomas W., 1919
  - Red Cross
    - American Red Cross, 1917-1918
    - Billings, Sherrard, 1917
    - Finley, John H., 1918
    - Stewart, William A. W., 1917-1918
  - Relief
    - Atherton, Gertrude, 1917
    - Metz, Herman A., 1917, 1919
    - Stallforth, F., 1916
  - Rumania
    - Clark, Charles U., 1919
    - Essary, Jesse F., 1918
    - Marie, queen of Rumania, 1919-1920, 1926
    - Misu, Nicholas, 1919
    - Vaida-Voevod, Alexandru, 1919
    - Vopicka, Charles J., 1919
  - Russia
    - Auchincloss, Gordon, 1918
    - Baldwin, George J., 1917
    - Bernstein, Herman, 1919
    - Bliss, Tasker H., 1918
    - Bullitt, William C., 1917
    - [Cantacuzene, Julia G.?], 1919
    - DuBois, Arthur W., 1919
    - Eyre, Lincoln, 1920
    - Francis, David R., 1916-1917, 1919
    - Hapgood, Norman, 1919
    - Harte, A. C., 1919
    - Hayes, George B., 1917
    - Hills, Lawrence, 1920
    - Lydig, Philip M., 1916-1917
    - Miles, Basil, 1916-1917
    - Mohrenschildt, F. de, 1918
    - Norodny, Ivan I., 1917
    - Patterson, A. M., 1920
    - Perkins, Thomas N., 1917
    - [Poublitoff, S.?], [1917?]
    - Reading, Rufus D. I., 1918
    - Ryan, Edward W., 1919-1920
    - Walling, William E., 1917
    - Wardwell, Allen, 1920
    - Whigham, Henry J., 1915
  - Scandinavia
    - Gunther, Franklin M., 1917-1918
  - Serbia
    - Glass, Carter, 1916
  - Shipping
    - Bedle, J. D., 1915
    - Brooks, Sydney, 1915, 1917
    - Brougham, Herbert B., 1916-1917
    - Brun, Constantin, 1917
    - Colby, Bainbridge, 1917
    - Cosgrave, John O., 1917
    - Cravath, Paul D., 1916
    - Gallauner, Edmund, 1919
    - Gardner, Augustus P., 1917
    - Gunther, Franklin M., 1918
    - Haight, Sandford and Smith, 1916
    - Heller, F. S., 1915-1916
    - Hewson, Hugh M., 1919
    - Hirst, William H., 1917
    - LeBlanc, Stewart A., 1919
    - Lord, Day and Lord, 1918
    - Mayer, Julius M., 1919
    - Milburn, Devereux, 1916
    - Neale, S. C., 1917
    - Nipgen, Alvin T., 1917
    - Proskey, W. Scott, 1917
    - Sheppard, Morris, 1916
    - Skinner, Robert P., 1916
    - Stone, Melville E., 1915, 1918
    - Thorne, Samuel, 1917, 1919
    - Van Slyke, Warren C., 1919
    - Vogelstein, Ludwig, 1916
    - Waterbury, Lawrence, 1920
    - Woolsey, Lester H., 1919
  - Spain
    - Creel, George, 1917-1918
    - Riano y Gayans, Don Juan, 1916-1917
    - Willard, Joseph E., 1917
  - State Department
    - Barondess, Joseph, 1919
    - Bayne, Hugh A., 1919
    - Beeckman, Robert L., 1917
    - Block, Rudolph, 1917
    - Boissevain, Eugen, 1916
    - Brown, James C., 1919
    - Bryant, Louise, 1918
    - Burnside, R. H., 1918-1919
    - Byrne, Helen M., 1919
    - Carey, Francis K., 1920
    - Cobbs, T. D., 1920
    - Cogswell, George E., 1919
    - Cummings, Homer S., 1920
    - Davis, Gherardi, 1918
    - Delafield, John R., 1920
    - Delehanty, James A., 1919
    - Dillon, Clarence, 1919
    - Dixon, Thomas D., 1920
    - Field, Walter S., 1919
    - Fletcher, Henry P., 1917-1920
    - Flournoy, James C., 1918, 1920
    - Francis, David R., 1919
    - Godet, Rose Marie, 1918
    - Grant, Ida H., 1919
    - Gregory, Thomas W., 1919
    - Grew, Joseph C., 1920
    - Gersdorff, Carl A. de, 1920
    - Hale, Edward J., 1920
    - Hammond, John H., 1919
    - Harrington, Herbert A., 1918-1919
    - Hayes, George B., 1919
    - Hewson, Hugh M., 1919
    - Jackson, William H., 1920
    - Jusserand, Jean, 1918
    - Kelley, Francis C., 1918-1919
    - Kellogg, Paul U., 1919
    - Lane, Franklin K., 1917
    - Legge, Alexander, 1919
    - Lindsay, Ronald C., 1920
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1920
    - Longworth, Nicholas, 1917
    - McCarthy, Thomas, 1918
    - Marshall, Thomas Riley, 1920
    - Olney, Richard, 1920
    - Redfield, William C., 1919
    - Saint Cyr, A. de, 1919
    - Shaw, G. Howland, 1920
    - Stanchfield, John B., 1917-1918
    - Stokes, Anson P., 1917
    - Swope, Herbert B., 1918
    - Totten, Ralph J., 1919
    - Underwood, Oscar J., 1919
    - Watriss, Frederic N., 1915-1916
    - Wickersham, George W., 1917
  - Sweden
    - Ekengren, Wilhelm A. F., 1917
    - Flint, Charles R., 1917
    - Morris, Ira N., 1918
  - Switzerland
    - [Godson, William F. H.?], 1918
    - Schelling, Ernest H., 1917-1918
    - Smith, Hoke, 1918
  - Trade
    - Anderson, Chandler P., 1915-1918
    - Anderson, Henry B., 1919
    - Armour, J. Ogden, 1916
    - Bible, Howard W., 1915
    - Bliss, Cornelius N., Jr., 1915
    - Borgfeldt (Geo.) and Co., 1915
    - Brandegee, Frank B., 1915-1916
    - Bride, William W., 1916
    - Cravath, Paul D., 1916
    - Davis, Gherardi, 1916
    - Debevoise, Thomas M., 1916
    - Dennett, Tyler, 1928-1929
    - Devlin, Martin P., 1917
    - Dulles, John F., 1916
    - Eastmond, A. H., 1915
    - Eisner, Mark, 1919
    - Ely, Richard, 1918
    - Faulkner, Charles J., Fr., 1917
    - Fort, John F., 1918
    - Garrison, Lindley M., 1916
    - Grimprel, U., 1918
    - Griscom, Lloyd C., 1915
    - Haight, Sandford and Smith, 1916
    - Hanson, Bert, 1919
    - Hardy, Charles J., 1916-1917
    - Hays, Arthur G., 1915
    - Herrick, Walter R., 1918
    - Hewson, Hugh M., 1919
    - Hitchcock, Gilbert M., 1919
    - Howland, Charles P., 1919
    - Kohns, Lee, 1915
    - Metz, Herman A., 1916
    - Moore, John Bassett, 1918
    - Olney, Richard, 1915-1916
    - Pittman, Key, 1915-1916
    - Redfield, William C., 1919
    - Robbins, Herbert D., 1918
    - Sheppard, Morris, 1915
    - Sherley, Swagar, 1916, 1918
    - Skiddy, W. W., 1915-1916
    - Skinner, Robert P., 1915-1916
    - Smith, Augustine J., 1917
    - Sonneborn (L.) Sons, 1917
    - Speyer and Co., 1916
    - Stancill, R. L., 1919
    - Stedman, Charles M., 1915
    - Wallerstein, David, 1916-1917
  - Treasury Department
    - Edwards, William, 1917
    - Houston, David F., 1917-1920
    - Leffingwell, Russell C., 1917
    - McAdoo, William G., 1917
    - Newton, Byron R., 1917
    - Rowe, Leo S., 1917, 1919-1920
    - Strauss, Albert, 1917
  - Turkey
    - Barton, James L., 1917
    - Beers, Lucius H., 1920
    - Bristol, Mark L., 1920-1921
    - Dodge, Cleveland H., 1916-1917
    - Moore, John Bassett, 1916
    - Patrick, Mary M., 1919
  - Venezuela
    - Fuller, Paul, Jr., 1918-1919
    - McGoodwin, Preston, 1918-1919
  - War Department
    - Baker, Newton D., 1917-1918
    - Biddle, John, 1917
    - Dyer, George R., 1916-1917
    - Hayes, George B., 1917-1918
  - War Industries Board
    - Anderson, Chandler P., 1918
    - Baruch, Bernard M., 1918
    - Perkins, Thomas N., 1918
  - War Trade Board
    - Meyer, Eugene, 1919
  - Yugoslavia
    - Vesnitch, Milenko R., 1919